Vanishing Point is a action, adventure, thriller film
directed by Charles Robert Carner.
When his wife goes into a troubled labor while he is on the road over 1200 miles away James Kowalski, an ex
race car driver and a former Army Ranger, attempts to elude police while trying to get home.
After numerous chases he turns into a Native American
reservation and reflects on his life, and his wife.
He heads off to break through a police roadblock.
Jimmy Kowalski, played by Viggo Mortensen.
Raphinia Kowalski, played by Christine Elise.
The Voice, played by Jason Priestley.
Sergeant Preston, played by Steve Railsback.
Motorcycle girl, played by Peta Wilson.
Vision Quest Indian, played by Rodney A. Grant.
Vanishing Point is a 1997 American action television film written and directed by Charles Robert Carner and
starring Viggo Mortensen, Jason Priestley, Peta Wilson, Christine Elise, and Keith David.
A remake of the 1971 film, it aired on the Fox
television network on January 7, 1997.
It features the same model 1970 Dodge Challenger R/T as the original film.
The tone is intense.